ganzestore.com 2013-06-07

# Ganz eStore: Buy Webkinz Pets, eStore Points, Deluxe Memberships, Online Items

  Updated May 13, 2013  

>     *  **Ganz is committed to protecting personal   information of its Service users and clients.**
>  
>     * **We don't knowingly collect personal   information from children under 13.  **
>  
>     * **Parents are urged to supervise their   children's activities online.**
>  
>     * **This policy applies to all information   that identifies a particular individual.**
>  
>     * **Personal information will be collected,   used and disclosed in accordance with the form of consent required by law.**
>  
>     * **Use of personal information is   limited.  **
>  
>     * **We take steps to protect personal   information.**
>  
>     * **We keep personal information for a   reasonable period of time only.**
>  
>     * **We may gather non-personal information   by means of cookies, beacons and other technology.**
>  
>     * **Ad companies collect anonymous   data.  You have options.  **
>  
>     * **Protect your personal information from   disclosure on social communication networks.**
>  
>     * **We provide links to third party websites   only as a convenience.  Make sure to  review their privacy policies.**
>  
>     * **You have control over certain of your   personal information. **
>  
>     * **You can ask privacy questions.**
>  
>     * **The Privacy Policy may change.   Review frequently.**
>  
>     * **This Privacy Policy contains special provisions   for users residing in California.  If  these are applicable to you, please review them carefully.**
> 

 **Ganz is committed to   protecting personal information of its Service users and clients.**

Ganz, an Ontario  partnership, together with its successors and assigns, is committed to  protecting the privacy and confidentiality of personal information entrusted to  us.  Ganz complies with Canadian Federal  and Provincial privacy laws and regulations including the Personal Information  Protection and Electronic Documents Act. Ganz will only use your personal  information for the purposes intended and as detailed in the Privacy Policy  unless we have obtained your consent to use it for other purposes. 

This Privacy Policy is  applicable to personally identifiable information ("PII") of all users  collected, stored or distributed through a website, mobile game or application  (commonly referred to as "Apps"), on which it is posted (collectively and  individually, "Service").  When this  Privacy Policy uses the term "PII" or "personal information", we mean  information that identifies a particular individual.  When certain other non-identifiable  information is directly associated with PII, this other information also becomes  PII for purposes of this Privacy Policy. Some jurisdictions may call personally  identifiable information "personal data" or "personally identifying  information," and may include opinions about or related to a user within the  definition of PII. 

This Privacy Policy is  designed to inform you about the information we collect and use and your  options with regard to that collection and use of that information through the  Service.  By use of the Service, or communications  to or with us, you are agreeing to these terms. If you do not agree with any of  these terms or the terms that govern the Service, please exit our site or  delete our mobile game or application and do not submit information to us in  any way.  By continued use of the Service  and/or clicking "I agree", you signify your consent to the collection and  processing of both your personal information and your child's user account  information, and any resulting correlation of such information, as set forth in  this Privacy Policy. 

When you provide us with  your or your child's personal information, you acknowledge that the information  will be stored and processed on servers located in Canada.  In the future, our business may require that  we contract with service providers outside Canada to carry out certain  functions on our behalf such as data back-up or storage.  In such situations, such service providers  will be contractually obliged not to disclose your and/or your child's personal  information except where authorized to do so by law or by Ganz.  Should a need to transfer your and/or your  child's personal information arise, we will ensure that the selected service  providers meet our privacy standards before we enter into contracts with them.  We will also require them to secure and maintain  confidentiality over your information.

 **We don't knowingly collect   personal information from children under 13.**

Some parts of the Service  offered by Ganz are not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not  knowingly collect information from children under this age through the Service. 

For the portions of the  Service that appeal directly to children under the age of 13, we incorporate  into this Privacy Policy the following additional children's privacy  provisions. When your child is asked to provide personal information, we will  provide you with an opportunity to consent to their disclosure of personal  information in accordance with applicable law. 

The information we collect  from you or your child enables participation in the Service.

  \- **Registration.   **During the registration  process, the child may be asked to set up a user name and password.  Your child should not use any personally  identifiable information as his or her user name, as this user name may be  visible to others on the Service. You and/or your child may be asked to provide  your email address to be used for recovering usernames and/or passwords.  \- **Surveys and Feedback:**  We may collect aggregate information in  connection with surveys or other online activities that allow your child to  give us feedback. We do not collect any personally identifiable information in  connection with surveys or feedback requests, nor is the information provided  connected to any personally identifiable information we may have about the  child.  \- **Service Management:**   We may collect information through technology  (such as logging IP addresses) for routine system  administration purposes, to make our Service more interesting and useful to you  and your child, or to manage content delivery. For instance, we collect  IP addresses and use technology to track traffic patterns on the Service. Once  your child has logged into the Service, we track your child's activities by  using logs of database transactions and server interactions. We also use this  information to understand which areas of our Service are most appealing or  least appealing and to deliver content that is specific to your country or area  of residence. The Service may also use cookies, which are pieces of information  that the Service sends to your child's computer while he or she is viewing the  Service. Cookies provide information to the Service so that the Service will  remember the user. These technical methods may involve the transmission of  information either directly to us or to our third party service providers who  are subject to the protections described in this Privacy Policy. None of the  information collected through these methods is connected to or associated with  any other information about your child.   \- **Email Communication from You:**   If your child contacts us by email or enters  an email address when participating in a contest, we use the email address only  to respond one time to your child's specific request and, if legally  permissible, to notify them if they won a contest.   \- **Mail Communication from You:   **If your child wants to  contact us by mail, and the Service provides a submission form for such  communication, you may do so using such submission form. The submission form  may ask for your child's user name and name of his or her game character, and  your (the parent's) name and signature.  \- **Chatting on the Service**.  When using scripted chat on any of the Service,  members select pre-constructed messages from chat menus. Members CANNOT type in  their own messages, and no personal information can be disclosed.    In the restricted chat mode, messages are  limited to words from our restricted dictionary, which is designed to prevent  minors from including any personal information such as numbers, common proper  names and place names.  Some areas of the  Service may offer unrestricted chat – such chat is suitable to adults but is  not to be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly permit  preteens to use unrestricted chat.   Please note that, in some instances, users relying on scripted chat may  view messages posted by users relying on the restricted and/or unrestricted  mode of chat. While users relying on scripted chat won't be able to disclose  their personal information, they may find content posted via  restricted/unrestricted chat objectionable.  \- **Safety and Security:** We  may collect your child's name and your email address as well as other personal  information, with applicable notice to you and consent, if necessary, for your  child's safety.  We may also collect your  child's name and email address for the limited purposes of protecting the  security and integrity of the Service, taking precautions against liability,  responding to the judicial process, as we may determine in our reasonable  judgment is advisable to protect our users, ourselves, our partners, agents and  providers, and the general public or for law enforcement on a matter related to  public safety.

 **Parents   are urged to supervise their children's activities online.**

Ganz urges all parents and  legal guardians to supervise their children's exploration of the Internet and  any online services, and to teach their children about protecting their  personal information online.  **If you reside in   the United States,** we encourage you to visit [http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec08.shtm](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec08.shtm) for  more information about COPPA and children's privacy.

If you are a parent or legal  guardian and will be purchasing licenses for codes to Service-related products  or services and sending the purchased codes to your child, please be advised  that such activity may correlate your child's user account information to your  personal information obtained during the purchase process. Although Ganz does  not generally correlate this data, in rare circumstances this may be necessary  to assist with your use of the Service, or otherwise. In compliance with applicable  laws we must inform you of the possible correlation and obtain your consent to  such correlation should it occur. 

**This policy applies to all   information that identifies a particular individual.**

When you interact with Ganz,  we may collect and store information from you directly as described below.  Ganz collects personal information that is  voluntarily provided by you when you order a product, enter promotions, answer  our polls or surveys, register on the Service, or communicate with us by mail,  telephone or electronically. Ganz also collects personal and non-personal  information automatically as described below. The type of information we  collect and maintain may include your name, mailing address, email address,  telephone number, gender, date of birth, purchase history,  chat room communications, complaints you may  have about our products or services, a record of promotions offered to you, and  your Ganz product preferences.  Other  information, such as your IP address, system information (including operating  system, browser type, available software and hardware), whether you were  referred to us by a search engine (including the search term(s) used to find  us), and how much time you spend using the Service are collected to improve the  Service and messaging efficiency, learn more about where our users come from  and understand how our users use and ways to improve our Service.

We may allow you to  "register" with us by using Facebook Connect or other Social Networking Service  ("SNS") authentication options to create an account or profile on the Service.

If you access the Service  from a third party SNS, you may be required to also read and accept the SNS  Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.  The  information you allow Ganz to access varies by game and SNS, and it is affected  by the privacy settings you establish at the SNS.  By accessing the Service through an SNS, you  are authorizing Ganz to collect, store, and use in accordance with the Privacy  Policy any and all information that you agreed the SNS could provide to Ganz  through the SNS Application Programming Interface ("API").  Your agreement takes place when you "accept"  or "allow" (or similar terms) one of our applications on an SNS.

 **Personal information will be   collected, used and disclosed in accordance with the form of consent required  by law.**

We reserve the right to  collect, use, and disclose your and/or your child's personal information  without consent where required or permitted by law.  Otherwise, personal information will be  collected, used and disclosed in accordance with the form of consent required  by applicable law and its use will be limited to the objectives for which it  was collected as described herein. The form of your consent can vary from  implied consent to express consent, depending on the circumstances and  sensitivity of the information collected. We will rely on implied consent when  we can reasonably conclude that you have given your consent by your action  (e.g. by giving us your name and contact information so that we may send you  the items ordered) or inaction (e.g. by not exercising an ability to opt-out).  This Privacy Policy identifies the purposes for which your personal information  is collected, used and disclosed. Additional consent will be obtained from you  should we wish to use or disclose your personal information for any additional  purpose.

 **Use of personal information is limited.**

Ganz collects personal  information for the following reasons:

  \- To provide you with the products or services  you have requested, including processing your payment;  \- To better understand you, to allow us to  serve you better through enhanced products, customer service and directed  promotional efforts of particular interest;  \- To properly investigate and respond to any  complaints, questions or concerns you may have about our products or services;  and  \- To determine your eligibility for our  products and the Service.

If you opt in to receive  offers, promotions or other information from Ganz, your information will be  used to provide you with promotional offers for Ganz products that we believe  may interest you and to solicit your opinion on our products and services. If  you have opted in to receive these offers, we may also use your personal  information to ensure that your contact information is accurate and up to date.  Ganz does not collect, use or disclose your  personal information for online behavioral advertising purposes.

Ganz  may share your and/or your child's personal information with the other members  of the Ganz corporate group, and their respective successors and assigns, but  only to the extent required to fulfill the purposes identified in this Privacy  Policy.  You may request that Ganz not  share your and/or your child's personal information with any of the other  members of the Ganz corporate group by contacting us as described below. 

In  addition to this inter-corporate sharing, Ganz may disclose personal  information to third parties as follows:

  \- **To Third Parties To   Perform Processing and Other Specialized Services:  **At times, Ganz may use outside organizations  to perform specialized services such as, but not limited to, legal and security  audits, payment processing, data analysis, e-mail delivery. These service  providers are only given the information needed to perform those services and  they are bound contractually to protect the confidentiality, privacy and  security of your information and to limit the use of your information to the  service being provided.    \- **To Third Parties in   the Event of Legal Reasons:  **We advise you that we  may disclose personal information to the government or other legal or  regulatory authorities (i) if so ordered by a court of law or (ii) for other  legal reasons, such as (a) to comply with legal process such as a search  warrant, subpoena or court order; (b) to protect the company's rights and  property; (c) to investigate reports of fraud or of users sending material  using a false email address or users sending harassing, threatening, or abusive  messages; (d) to protect against what we believe in our sole and absolute  discretion to be a misuse or unauthorized use of our Service; or (e) in  emergencies, such as when we believe our or our affiliate's integrity requires  protection or someone's physical safety is at risk.  In some cases, disclosure may be required by  law to be without notice to you.   \- **To a Third Party in   the Event of a Significant Transaction or Other Event: **In the case of any  significant transaction or event involving Ganz or any of its related entities  or divisions such as, by way of example, a sale, merger, amalgamation, financing,  re-organization, liquidation, or insolvency, other parties to the transaction  and their professional advisors may need to have access to Ganz's customer  lists and various databases as part of the due diligence process. In this  event, Ganz would only provide such access under terms of a strict  confidentiality agreement. Also, upon completion of the transaction or event,  your personal information would be transferred to Ganz's successor-in-interest  to be used only for the purposes for which it was collected.

 **  
We take steps to protect   personal information.**

Ganz has implemented  physical, electronic and administrative measures to protect your information  from error, loss or unauthorized access. For example, we use industry-standard  efforts, such as passwords, firewalls and Secure Socket Layers, to safeguard  the confidentiality of your personal information contained on our computer  systems. In addition, our employees and any third parties we use are  contractually bound to protect the confidentiality of your information and  access is restricted to those with a need to know the information to carry out  the identified purpose.

 **We keep personal information   for a reasonable period of time only.**

We keep your information for  a period reasonably necessary to meet the purposes for which it was collected,  for the security of Ganz and the Service or to protect users, the public or  third parties and to comply with any legal requirements, including statutory  retention periods and corporate best practices. 

**We may gather non-personal   information by means of cookies, beacons and other technology.**

We may gather non-personal  information on an anonymous, aggregate basis.   This information is not kept, used or disclosed at the individual level,  but may be disclosed to third parties on an anonymous, aggregate basis. We may  collect such information through unique identifiers such as cookies (which may  be HTML files, Flash files, or other technology), web beacons, or similar  technologies for analytical purposes, routine system administration, to make  our Service more interesting and useful to you, or to manage content delivery.  For instance, 

  \- We use technology to track traffic patterns  on the Service. Once you have logged into the Service, we track your activities  by using logs of database transactions and server interactions. We also use  this information to understand which areas of our Service are most appealing or  least appealing or to deliver content that is specific to your country or area  of residence;  \- We use cookies, small text files stored on  your hard drive, not our Service, which allow you to store your password  without having to constantly re-enter it. Cookies also help us to tailor  messages that better match your needs and interests, and they allow us to  better understand how users in general use the Service, which in turn helps us  to focus our resources on features that are most popular with our users. 

**Ad companies collect   anonymous data.  You have options.  **

From time to time, we may  use third-party advertising service providers to serve ads on the Service.  These companies may use cookie-based ad serving technology for the purpose of  (i) ad delivery and reporting; and (ii) re-targeting and/or online advanced  targeting, provided, however, that your visit to our Service shall be excluded  from your online profile used for such advertising purposes.  Furthermore, to monitor usage or transfer of  content to another site or location and to collect advertising metrics, such  third parties may include in the content web beacons or clear GIFs.  Clear GIFs (a.k.a. web bugs, beacons or tags)  are small graphic images placed on a web page, web-based document, or in an  e-mail message.  Clear GIFs are invisible  to the user because they are typically very small and the same colour as the  background of the web page, document or e-mail message.  Because your web browser must request such  content from the third parties' servers, such third parties can track your  usage, or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from  their site. 

Although the third-party  advertising service providers may not have access to tracking technologies set  by Ganz, or any of your personal information collected on the Service, they may  themselves set and access their own tracking technologies and/or they may  otherwise have access to information about you. The use of such technology by  these third parties is within their control and not ours. Even if Ganz has a  relationship with the third party, it does not control their sites or policies  and practices regarding your information. 

This Privacy Policy does not  cover any use of information that third-party advertising service providers or  advertisers may collect from you. We encourage you to investigate and ask  questions directly of them in this regard. If you would like more information  about the practices used by third-party advertising service providers and  advertisers and to know your choices about not having the information gathered  used by these companies, visit [http://networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).  Please note that Flash cookies operate  differently than browser cookies and cookie management tools available in a web  browser will not remove Flash cookies.   To learn more about and manage Flash cookies, visit [www.adobe.com](http://www.adobe.com/) and  make changes at the privacy setting panel.   You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but  some parts of the Service may not work properly if you do. 

We have given users of  webkinz.com (except Alumni and free users) an option to limit third party  ads.  To opt out, parents should visit  the "Account Controls" section of the Parent's Area  and select the limit ads option.  Please note that the option is not available  to Free and Alumni Webkinz users but they may still be able to opt out of third  party cookies by following the steps outlined by your web browser provider.  If, after users have selected to limit 3rd party ads, they clear their computer's cache and/or cookies, or access  webkinz.com from another computer, they will need to limit 3rd party  ads again in order to prevent 3rd party ads from appearing on the  home, login, and logout pages, as well as pages that follow the logout page. If  users do not select to limit 3rd party ads again, 3rd party ad campaigns within webkinz.com will still be limited.

 **Protect your personal   information from disclosure on social communication networks.**

Please note that any  information that you submit in online chat rooms and public user profiles, on  message boards or in similar forums on the Service can be read, collected, or  used by others.  Your passwords should be  both easy to remember, but hard to guess and not shared with anyone (other than  a child sharing their passwords with their parents or legal guardians). You  should not access your account from a shared computer or device or a public  computer or device to avoid the unauthorized accessing of your account. It is  recommended that you not store your logins/passwords on your computer or device  in case it falls into the hands of someone else. Please note that Ganz is not  responsible for information you choose to submit in the forums, nor anyone  accessing your account through the use of your passwords or otherwise. 

**We provide links to third   party websites only as a convenience.   Make sure to review their privacy policies.**

While using the Service, you  may, through hypertext or other computer "links," gain access to other websites  on the Internet which are not operated by Ganz. Ganz is providing these links  to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply  endorsement by Ganz of the website linked to. WHILE THESE LINKS HAVE BEEN  REVIEWED AT THE TIME THEY ARE POSTED, WEBSITES AND SERVICES CHANGE FROM TIME TO  TIME AND WE CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT THEY REMAIN APPROPRIATE FOR CHILDREN, SAFE,  PRIVATE OR SECURE. GANZ ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY MATERIAL OUTSIDE OF  THE SERVICE, INCLUDING ANY WEBSITES WHICH MAY BE ACCESSED THROUGH A LINK ON THE  SERVICE. Unless otherwise indicated on the Service, Ganz is not sponsored by or  affiliated with the linked websites, and trademarks used in connection with the  linked websites are not trademarks of Ganz. You should be aware that each of  these third-party websites or services is governed by a different set of terms  and policies with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of your  personal information. Make sure to review their privacy policies before using  them and preview them for appropriate content before allowing your children to  access them.

 **You have control over certain   of your personal information. **

You have choices over how we  collect, use and disclose certain of your personal information for certain  purposes. Those have been indicated below. But note that if you use the  Service, you must agree to our terms of use and the terms of this Privacy  Policy without exception. Any comments or questions you may have regarding the  collection, use and disclosure of your personal information should be directed  to Ganz.

You may choose not to  receive certain email from us, even after granting permission initially, by unsubscribing.  Instructions on how to unsubscribe from emails that are not related to  processing of your transactions with us are included in each such email. (You  may not unsubscribe from communications related to your Account administration  or the processing of your transactions.)   Certain jurisdictions require that we provide a copy of the personal  information we have on file about your or your child. If your jurisdiction  requires this, unless otherwise required by applicable law, all requests for a  copy of the personal information we have on file about you, and requests to  delete such information, must be made in writing and by postal mail addressed  to: Privacy Officer, Ganz, One Pearce Road, Woodbridge, Ontario, L4L 3T2,  Canada. Ganz may require that you identify yourself to our satisfaction. In the  event that you are unable to identify yourself or your legal rights to obtain  your child's personal information we have on file, Ganz may, consistent with  applicable law, decline to provide this information. If we so decline, we will  provide the reason(s).

Personal information  provided by email may not be secure, and   you assume the risks associated with your email transmission or our  reply.

 **You can ask privacy   questions.**

If you have any questions or  comments about Ganz's Privacy Policy, or need to contact us with respect to a  privacy concern, please contact us at [privacyofficer@ganz.com](mailto:privacyofficer@ganz.com) by email.  (Children should have their parents submit any questions or comments on their  behalf.) You can also write to: Privacy Officer, Ganz, One Pearce Road,  Woodbridge, Ontario, L4L 3T2, Canada, or submit your inquiry via facsimile:  905-851-7427. ****

 **The Privacy Policy may   change.  Review frequently.**

This Privacy Policy outlines  the information usage practices of Ganz. By accessing, browsing or using this  Service or by submitting your and/or your child's personal information to Ganz,  you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not submit personal  information to us or use the Service. 

We reserve the right to  modify this Privacy Policy and our terms of service at any time and from time  to time. If there is a material change to our information usage practices that  affects your personal information, you will be notified of such change by a  conspicuous posting on the Service. You may also be prompted to elect whether  or not you agree to the change, if required by applicable law. Note that you  may be unable to utilize the Service if you choose not to agree to a  modification to this Privacy Policy. If any future change affects our payment  processing and order fulfillment functions, if you withhold your consent, we  may not be able to continue to process payments or fulfill orders from you.  Your acceptance of a revised Privacy Policy, which may be communicated by  clicking to indicate your consent for the continued use of the Service or the provision  of your personal information to Ganz following the effective date of any  changes to this Privacy Policy shall mean that you have accepted those changes.

 **This Privacy Policy contains   special provisions for users residing in California.  If these are applicable to you, please review  them carefully.**

Under California Civil Code  Section 1798.83 (also known as S.B. 27 or the "Shine the Light" law), if you  are a California resident and your business relationship with Ganz is primarily  for personal, family, or household purposes, you may request certain data  regarding Ganz's disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties  for the third-parties' direct marketing purposes. To make such a request,  please send an email message to [privacyofficer@ganz.com](mailto:privacyofficer@ganz.com) with  "Request for California Privacy Information" in the subject line; you  may make such a request up to once per calendar year. If applicable, we will  provide you, by email, a list of the categories of personal information  disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the  immediately preceding calendar year, along with the third parties' names and  addresses. Please note that not all personal information sharing is covered by  S.B. 27's requirements.
